if we
만약 우리가
Are we really going to be undetected?
우리는 정말로 발각되지 않을 것인가?
nothing is absolute
아무것도 절대적인 것은 아니다
remember
기억하다
right now we
지금 우리는
in the same boat
같은 배에서
if something happens to you
당신에게 무슨 일이 생기면
Huang Zicheng and I are done
황쯔쳉과 나는 끝났어
Do not hesitate
주저하지 말고
we should
우리는해야한다
we must do this
우리는 이것을 해야 해
you come from night fog
너는 밤안개에서 왔구나
You must bear these consequences
당신은 이러한 결과를 감수해야합니다
I want to save Huang Ziqing
황자칭을 구하고 싶다
no other choice
다른 선택은 없어
concept?
개념?
Understood
이해했다
from now on
지금부터
Everything is under my arrangement
모든 것은 내 합의 하에 있다
Do you want an injection?
주사 맞으시겠어요?
I didn't know until I was in college
대학 다닐 때까지는 몰랐어요
Inject from injection bag
주사백에서 주사
He remains in a coma.
그는 여전히 혼수상태에 빠져 있습니다.
He continues to inject
계속 주사를 놓는군요
This is more subtle
이게 더 미묘하네요
Easy to move
이동이 용이함
OK
좋아요
follow me
나를 따라와
This is a monitoring site
모니터링 사이트입니다
Our biggest problem now
지금 우리의 가장 큰 문제
He avoided this surveillance
그는 이 감시를 피했다
and made me a nurse
그리고 나를 간호사로 만들어줬어요
therefore
그러므로
no one will look at me
아무도 나를 쳐다보지 않을 거야
We can't just think about sports
스포츠만 생각할 수는 없다
we don't care about the consequences
우리는 결과에 대해 신경 쓰지 않습니다
Our work has two results
우리의 작업에는 두 가지 결과가 있습니다.
one
하나
it was found
그것은 발견되었다
operation failed
작업 실패
two
둘
mission accomplished
임무 완수
They pulled it out successfully
성공적으로 꺼냈어요
No matter which
상관없이
They'll find surveillance footage
그들은 감시 영상을 찾을 것입니다
to figure it out
그것을 알아 내기 위해
so we have to leave
그래서 우리는 떠나야 해
in order to mitigate the impact
충격을 완화하기 위해
but here
하지만 여기는
There is a lot of surveillance
감시가 많네요
avoid them completely
완전히 피하세요
Absolutely impossible
절대 불가능
So we have to find a way to fool them
그래서 우리는 그들을 속일 수 있는 방법을 찾아야 합니다
i can make up for it
내가 보상할 수 있어
Don't let the camera catch me
카메라에 들키지 마세요
it can cover up the appearance
그 모습을 가릴 수 있다
but shape
하지만 모양
It's not easy to hide
숨기는 게 쉽지 않죠
especially you
특히 당신
In the eyes of the National Security Office
국가안보실의 눈으로
some people are sensitive to you
어떤 사람들은 당신에게 예민해요
What should we do?
우리는 무엇을 해야 합니까?
no trace
흔적이 없다
impossible
불가능한
Only eye illusions can be used
착시현상만 사용할 수 있습니다.
if they investigate
그들이 조사한다면
we will let them
우리는 그들에게 허락할 것이다
Wrong direction
잘못된 방향
can we do it
우리가 할 수 있을까?
unnecessary
불필요한
First consider the following things
먼저 다음 사항을 고려하십시오.
It's not hard to get rid of it
없애는 건 어렵지 않아요
hard
딱딱한
Can be safely recovered when the job is done
작업 완료 후 안전하게 복구 가능
How should we treat them?
우리는 그들을 어떻게 대해야 할까요?
I'll find a way to keep them away from me
난 그들이 나에게서 멀어지도록 하는 방법을 찾을 거예요
from noon
정오부터
afternoon
오후
Guard her in the room
그녀를 방에서 지켜라
Entering during a weak period
비수기 진입
What time is it exactly now?
지금이 정확히 몇시입니까?
Four p.m
오후 4시
Xiao Yi went to the second floor to check
샤오이는 확인을 위해 2층으로 갔다
you have to catch it
넌 그걸 잡아야 해
at the door of the room
방 문에서
when the time comes
때가되면
I'll go check the surveillance video
감시 영상 확인하러 갈게요
Where should I hide?
어디에 숨어야 할까요?
Toilet
화장실
What if someone comes in?
누군가 들어오면 어쩌지?
this bathroom
이 화장실
I prepare it for patients
환자들을 위해 준비합니다
Xiao Yi is in a coma
샤오이는 혼수상태에 빠졌어요
he won't enter
그 사람은 들어가지 않을 거야
doctors and nurses
의사와 간호사
Close the door after entering
입장 후 문을 닫아주세요
Wait until I notify you before taking action
조치를 취하기 전에 알림을 받을 때까지 기다리세요.
If any problems arise
어떤 문제가 발생하면
i will solve the problem
내가 문제를 해결해줄게
OK
좋아요
when i finish moving
내가 이사를 마치면
When will I go out?
나는 언제 나갈 것인가?
I'll give you a sign
사인을 드릴게요
do you remember?
기억 나니?
almost
거의
almost impossible
거의 불가능한
we must succeed
우리는 성공해야 해
cannot fail
실패할 수 없다
if you fail
실패하면
we will get it done
우리는 그것을 끝낼 것이다
I can
저 할 수 있어요
I remind you
나는 당신에게 상기시켜줍니다
don't drink water
물을 마시지 마세요
OK
좋아요
Let's start
시작하자
have you heard of it
의 대해서 들어 봤나
Did you hear it?
들었어?
Xiaoyi production
샤오이 생산
Rescue ineffectiveness
구조의 무능함
I've prepared the medicine
약을 준비했어요
To them
그들에게
are you ready?
준비 되었나요?
I can anytime
난 언제든지 할 수 있어
Good luck
행운을 빌어요
come and breathe
와서 숨을 쉬어
do not move
이동하지 않습니다
Your technique is good
기술이 좋으시네요
I learned from the National Security Bureau
국가안전보위부에서 배웠어요
Stop talking nonsense
말도 안되는 소리 그만해
I tell you
나는 당신에게 말한다
I told you
내가 말했잖아
I'll give it back to you
내가 다시 돌려줄게
OK
좋아요
You can disembark now
이제 하선할 수 있습니다
How can I get off the bus?
버스에서 어떻게 내릴 수 있나요?
tell the boat
배에 말하다
Return to Tianhai immediately
즉시 텐하이로 돌아가세요
do you think they are
당신은 그들이 그렇다고 생각합니까?
Obey your orders?
당신의 명령에 복종하시겠습니까?
OK
좋아요
I'll let you taste it
맛보게 해줄게
What does fear feel like?
두려움은 어떤 느낌인가요?
What?
무엇?
do not move
이동하지 않습니다
Have you ever killed anyone?
누군가를 죽인 적이 있나요?
You do not dare
당신은 감히하지 않습니다
or not?
아니면?
I thought you weren't afraid of death.
나는 당신이 죽음을 두려워하지 않는다고 생각했습니다.
There are no bullets in this gun
이 총에는 총알이 없습니다
What's your job?
당신의 직업은 무엇입니까?
stay away
떨어져있어
What does ancient Chinese mean?
고대 중국어는 무엇을 의미합니까?
if you don't have enough
만약 당신이 충분하지 않다면
my grandson
내 손자
are you serious?
너 진심이야?
enjoy it
즐겨라
Oh grandson
아 손자야
(Rao K).
(라오 K).
science science
과학 과학
Am I late?
내가 늦었나요?
Shall we have dinner together soon?
조만간 같이 저녁 먹을까요?
I dont go
나는 가지 않는다
I'm going to Chen's office
나 첸 사무실로 갈게
Report news
뉴스보고
Enter
입력하다
Mr. Chen
첸 씨
Wow that
와 그거
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
It's nothing, I just came to see it
별거 아니야 그냥 보러 왔어
What happened to him?
그에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
He must anoint one
그는 한 사람에게 기름을 부어야 한다
therefore
그러므로
I leave, you stay
나는 떠나고 너는 남아
OK
좋아요
let's go
갑시다
You two go relax
너희 둘은 가서 쉬어라
I'll watch it here
여기서 볼게요
OK
좋아요
please
제발
When will you show up?
언제 나타날 거예요?
When will you go out?
언제 나갈 거예요?
OK, just a second
네, 잠시만요
Let me check it for you.
제가 확인해 보겠습니다.
0401...
0401...
The results will be announced tomorrow morning.
결과는 내일 오전에 발표됩니다.
tomorrow morning
내일 아침
Okay, thank you
좋아 감사합니다
You're welcome
천만에요
Who's working tonight?
오늘 밤에는 누가 일해요?
until eight o'clock
여덟시까지
Afterwards, Da Liu and Xiao Ma
그 후 Da Liu와 Xiao Ma가
If something happens tonight
오늘 밤에 무슨 일이 생기면
our club
우리 클럽
Okay, thank you
좋아 감사합니다
Thanks
감사해요
Tian Yang is not here
천양은 여기 없어
No, what's wrong?
아니, 무슨 일이야?
Xiangyang's Love Poems
향양의 사랑시
The secret has been solved
비밀이 풀렸어요
after that?
이후?
do you remember
기억 나니
Huang Zicheng took the photo
황자성이 사진을 찍다
forward
앞으로
Xiang Yang also took a portion
Xiang Yang도 일부를 차지했습니다.
you mean
네 말 뜻은
That night fog is already known
그 밤안개는 이미 알려져 있어
Huang Ziqing has changed the data inside
Huang Ziqing이 내부 데이터를 변경했습니다.
correct
옳은
so i want
그래서 내가 원해
Tell Tianyang
텔양에게 전하세요
I know I'll tell him
나는 그에게 말할 것이라는 것을 안다.
Okay, thank you
좋아 감사합니다
Thanks
감사해요
Leo
사자 별자리
Where is Gao Tianyang?
가오텐양은 어디에 있나요?
he went to the hospital
그는 병원에 갔다
We will be on duty tonight
우리 오늘 밤 근무할 거야
Aren't you and Xiaoma on duty?
당신과 Xiaoma는 근무 중이 아니신가요?
they changed
그들은 변했다
I will go with you
나는 당신과 함께 갈 것이다
.I have something to find.
.찾을 게 있어요.
(Gao Jie).
(가오 지에).
Have you eaten yet?
아직 식사하셨나요?
not yet
아직 아님
I packed some things
몇 가지 물건을 챙겼어요
in restaurant
레스토랑에서
Go to eat quickly
빨리 먹으러 가세요
you go first
니가 먼저가
I will follow him here
나는 여기에서 그를 따라갈 것이다
No, you two go together
아니요, 둘이 같이 가요
I'm here
나는 여기 있다
OK
좋아요
Thanks
감사해요
I came back so quickly
너무 빨리 돌아왔어
Kill quickly
빨리 죽여라
OK
좋아요
I'm a little bored. I want to go down and get some air.
좀 심심해서 내려가서 바람 좀 쐬고 싶어요.
Do you want coffee?
커피 마실 래요?
I'll buy you two pairs of glasses
안경 두 개 사줄게
Forget it, Gok
잊어버려, 고크
There are rules in the hospital
병원에는 규칙이 있어요
Bringing is not allowed here
이곳은 반입이 금지되어 있습니다
yes i forgot
응 잊어버렸어
ขาด oxygen your brain is bad
ขг 산소 당신의 두뇌는 나쁘다
I gotta go.
난 가야 해.
Patient No. 0401's heart suddenly stopped beating
0401번 환자의 심장이 갑자기 멈췄습니다.
You need to be rescued immediately.
즉시 구출해야 합니다.
What's wrong?
뭐가 문제 야?
The patient's heart suddenly stopped
환자의 심장이 갑자기 멈췄다.
I'll treat him now
이제 내가 그 사람을 치료해줄게
come over
이리와
The ambulance is quick
구급차가 빨라요
what happened
무슨 일이에요
Xiao Yi looked a little strange
샤오이는 좀 이상해 보였어
I don't know what happened
무슨 일이 일어났는지 모르겠어요
He immediately informed Director Chen
그는 즉시 첸 감독에게 알렸다.
exhibit
전시하다
Xiaoyi encountered some problems
Xiaoyi는 몇 가지 문제에 직면했습니다.
I don't know what's going on
무슨 일인지 모르겠어요
Give Way
방법을 제공
keep away
멀리하다
Come quickly
빨리 오세요
OK
좋아요
Understood
이해했다
Be prepared for electric shock
감전에 대비하세요
OK
좋아요
I have been informed
나는 정보를 받았다
Understood
이해했다
Are you OK?
괜찮으세요?
he died
그는 죽었다
How could he die?
그가 어떻게 죽을 수 있었습니까?
It happened suddenly
갑자기 일어난 일이야
I don't know what happened
무슨 일이 일어났는지 모르겠어요
Xiao Chen and Xiao Jiang are looking for surveillance cameras
Xiao Chen과 Xiao Jiang은 감시 카메라를 찾고 있습니다.
This was too sudden, something went wrong
너무 갑작스러워서 뭔가 잘못됐어
where are you going?
어디 가세요?
peace room
평화의 방
I'll go in and have a look
내가 들어가서 좀 볼게
Follow me to the observation room
나를 따라 관찰실로 가세요
Go first
먼저가
I'll find you soon
곧 찾아갈게요
OK
좋아요
Arrive at third floor A
3층 A에 도착
Building 3A
3A동
What exactly is going on?
정확히 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 걸까요?
we do not know
우리는 모른다
Okay, thank you
좋아 감사합니다
Thanks
감사해요
You're welcome
천만에요
always.
언제나.
How is monitoring going?
모니터링은 어떻게 진행되고 있나요?
All previous surveillance cameras
이전의 모든 감시 카메라
has been cleaned up
청소되었습니다
they are empty
그들은 비어있다
Why
왜
I just asked the nurse
방금 간호사한테 물어봤는데
she said all videos
그녀는 모든 비디오를 말했어
All videos
모든 동영상
weekly
주간
What a coincidence
이런 우연이
Already cleaned today
오늘은 이미 청소했어
You've already asked us
당신은 이미 우리에게 요청했습니다
All surveillance videos
모든 감시 비디오
Engineering Department Design
공학부 디자인
Design time is ten days
디자인 기간은 열흘
they do not know
그들은 모른다
Who was present when the accident occurred?
사고가 일어났을 때 그 자리에 누가 있었나요?
we are all here
우리는 모두 여기에 있습니다
Where is Gao Tianyang?
가오텐양은 어디에 있나요?
He said he wanted to come down and take a breath
내려와서 한숨 쉬고 싶다고 하더군요
We also asked
우리도 물어봤어
Do you want to buy a cup of coffee?
커피 한 잔 사시겠어요?
Had anyone been here before the accident?
사고 전에 여기에 와본 사람이 있었나요?
no one has ever come
아무도 온 적 없어
What's up?
무슨 일이야?
No
아니요
Understood
이해했다
what are you looking for
무엇을 찾고 계신가요
See if anyone is suspicious
의심스러운 사람이 있는지 살펴보세요.
look
바라보다
That woman is in the last row
그 여자는 맨 마지막 줄에 있어요
again
다시
There is a surveillance camera at the entrance of the intensive care unit
중환자실 입구에 감시카메라가 설치되어 있습니다.
look
바라보다
Xiao Yi's body
샤오이의 시체
When being sent to the Peace Room
평화의 방으로 보내질 때
this person
이 사람
He takes special care of him
그는 그를 특별하게 보살펴준다
I follow her
나는 그녀를 따른다
Do you doubt this person?
이 사람을 의심하시나요?
It has something to do with Xiao Yi’s death
샤오이의 죽음과 관련이 있습니다
Maybe he sent me mist
어쩌면 그 사람이 나한테 안개를 보냈을지도 모르지
Investigate Xiao Yi
샤오이를 조사하세요
again
다시
underground surveillance camera
지하 감시 카메라
look at this man
이 사람 좀 봐
It's the same person in the corridor
복도에 똑같은 사람이네
in the corridor
복도에서
change your clothes
옷을 갈아입으세요
but i'm not sure
하지만 잘 모르겠어
Is she alone?
그녀는 혼자인가요?
Why don't you leave?
떠나는 게 어때?
she changed clothes
그녀는 옷을 갈아입었다
Is there a purpose?
목적이 있나요?
I gonna go see
보러 갈게
I will go with you
나는 당신과 함께 갈 것이다
Stay and continue investigating.
남아서 계속 조사해 보세요.
Mr. Sir
선생님
wake up sir
일어나세요 선생님
Come and sit
와서 앉으세요
Are you OK
괜찮으세요
I feel dizzy
어지러워
I feel dizzy. What happened?
현기증이 나요. 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
it seems
것 같다
Someone hit
누군가 쳤어
Have you ever been beaten?
구타당한 적 있나요?
Are you seeing a man or a woman?
남자를 만나나요, 여자를 만나나요?
No
아니요
Put on a cap
모자를 쓰세요
peaked cap
정점
Yes
예
Leo, come to the Peace Room.
레오, 평화의 방으로 오세요.
someone fainted
누군가 기절했다
come to help
도와주러 와
You are Mr. Zhang
당신은 장 씨입니다
Let me go
나를 보내줘
you caused me
네가 나에게 원인이 됐어
This brings up a big problem for me
이것은 나에게 큰 문제를 가져온다
you can solve it
당신은 그것을 해결할 수 있습니다
i am safe
나는 안전 해
you are safe
당신은 안전합니다
where is he?
그 사람은 어디 있어?
get away
도망가다
Do you see your face clearly?
얼굴이 또렷하게 보이나요?
No
아니요
Look at the picture
사진을 봐
Must be at the bar
바에 있어야 해
The person who hits the other person
상대방을 때리는 사람
Mr. Zhang
장 씨
perhaps
아마도
I went to the standing room of the corpse.
나는 시체 입석실로 갔다.
Is she sure about Xiao Yi's body?
그녀는 샤오이의 몸을 확신하고 있나요?
perhaps
아마도
I identified the body
시체를 확인했어요
This means Xiao Yi is dead
샤오이가 죽었다는 뜻이다
did not do so
그러지 않았다
There is another person
다른 사람이 있어요
Are you hiding something from me?
나한테 뭔가 숨기고 있는 거 있어?
I've known you for a long time
나는 당신을 오랫동안 알고 있었어요
i know this
나는이 사실을 알고
when you have something on your mind
마음속에 뭔가 있을 때
therefore
그러므로
This is the expression
이 표현은
i have to change it
나 그거 바꿔야 해
Don't worry
괜찮아요
Others don't see this
다른 사람들은 이 내용을 볼 수 없습니다.
unless you're worried
걱정하지 않는 한
become our rival
우리의 라이벌이 되자
If one day
만약 어느 날
you won't let me go
당신은 나를 놓아주지 않을 것입니다
It's like I've committed a crime
마치 내가 범죄를 저지른 것 같아
you will cover me
너는 나를 덮을 것이다
Don't want to explain
설명하고 싶지 않아
Huang Zicheng lost contact
황자성은 연락이 끊겼다
Xiao Yi died suddenly
샤오이가 갑자기 사망했어요
Mr. Zhang appeared in the morgue
장 씨가 영안실에 나타났습니다
these things
이런 일
There are relationships
관계가 있습니다
Yes or no
예 혹은 아니오
Yes
예
this is your plan
이것이 당신의 계획입니다
Guo An suspects Xiao Yi's death
궈안은 샤오이의 죽음을 의심한다
Sent for autopsy
부검을 위해 보냄
Unable to identify body
시체를 식별할 수 없습니다
But he must be dead
하지만 그 사람은 죽었나 봐요
Where is Gao Tianyang?
가오텐양은 어디에 있나요?
let me go
날 보내줘
he recognized you
그 사람이 당신을 알아보았어요
perhaps
아마도
This is better
이게 낫다
In fact, as long as you cooperate
사실, 당신이 협력하는 한
will be easier
더 쉬울 것이다
I hope so
나는 희망한다
Hello
안녕하세요
Please take a seat
자리에 앉으세요
good fish
좋은 물고기
He has just been transferred from Na'vi
그는 방금 Na'vi에서 이적했습니다.
Is there anything to eat at this late hour?
이 늦은 시간에 먹을 것이 있나요?
Am I lucky?
나는 운이 좋은가?
I reserved it just for you
당신만을 위해 예약했어요
Really?
정말?
you seem to know
당신은 알고있는 것 같아요
I will come tonight
오늘 밤에 올게요
Yes
예
woman's intuition
여자의 직감
Yes or no
예 혹은 아니오
when you first came
네가 처음 왔을 때
you know
알잖아
I will become a regular visitor here
나는 이곳의 단골 손님이 될 것이다
you are a special guest
당신은 특별한 손님이에요
different from others
남들과 다르다
It's too late now
이제 너무 늦었어
let's get the job done
일을 끝내자
good sister
좋은 여동생
These are precious materials
귀한 자료들이네요
it doesn't suit me
그것은 나에게 적합하지 않습니다
they will invite me today
오늘 날 초대할 거야
impossible
불가능한
I have to pay for food
밥값은 내가 내야지
I'm worried I can't afford the fees
수수료를 감당할 수 없을까 걱정됩니다
you want
당신이 원하는
To get rid of me?
나를 없애려고?
No
아니요
i got hurt today
나 오늘 다쳤어
I can't eat cold food
차가운 음식을 못 먹거든요
Can't drink
마실 수 없다
drink tea
차를 마시다
OK
좋아요
what happened to your hand?
네 손은 어떻게 됐어?
perhaps
아마도
He's been holding a knife for a long time
그는 오랫동안 칼을 쥐고 있었습니다
you must protect yourself
당신은 자신을 보호해야합니다
I can
저 할 수 있어요
How did you hurt your arm?
팔은 어떻게 다치셨나요?
have a friend
친구가 있어요
scratched with knife
칼로 긁힌
any friend
어떤 친구라도
you are not careful
너는 조심하지 않는다
Yes
예
I don't know if this is intentional
이게 의도적인지는 모르겠지만
Or accidentally?
아니면 우연히?
seriously injured
심각하게 부상당한
I think
제 생각에는
Discuss
논의하다
Her knife is extraordinary
그녀의 칼은 특별하다
cut fish like a knife
칼처럼 생선을 자르다
as sharp as a knife
칼처럼 날카로운
Luckily she didn't use a gun
다행히 그녀는 총을 사용하지 않았다
Guns cannot be used casually
총은 함부로 사용할 수 없습니다
This is in China
이것은 중국에 있습니다.
not in the united states
미국에는 없어
Getting fired is a big deal
해고당하는 건 큰 일이야
correct
옳은